Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series XCVIII. 1943 CONVENTION
  - Sub-Series 477-122. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 122
    - Demand two weeks' vacation for all laborers under Clerks' Agreement, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 55)
  - Sub-Series 477-123. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 123
    - Brotherhood to require that railroads furnish detailed statement of deductions from paycheck, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 56)
  - Sub-Series 477-124. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 124
    - Establish uniform rates of pay for similar work in a particular district, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 57)
  - Sub-Series 477-125. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 125
    - Distribute officers of Boards of Adjustment equally among lodges under jurisdiction of such Boards of Adjustment, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 58)
  - Sub-Series 477-126. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 126
    - Require three years' continuous membership before election as officer or member of Protective Committee, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 59)
  - Sub-Series 477-127. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 127
    - Grand President to seek changes in Rules 68, 70, and 75(b) of Express Agreement, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 60)
  - Sub-Series 477-128. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 128
    - Amend Rule 21 of Express Agreement, to require employees transferring to other districts to stay 90 days or until seniority is exhausted, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 61)
  - Sub-Series 477-129. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 129
    - Eliminate short-hour provision from Express Agreement, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 62)
  - Sub-Series 477-130. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 130
    - Amend Rules 53 and 55 and Addendum A, Express Agreement, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 63)
  - Sub-Series 477-131. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 131
    - Change "short-turn-around" rule in Express Agreement to 150 miles, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 64)
  - Sub-Series 477-132. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 132
    - Request two weeks' vacation after three years' service for all members, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 65)
  - Sub-Series 477-133. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 133
    - Night work should be paid for at 10 per cent above the prevailing rate for day work, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 66)
  - Sub-Series 477-134. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 134
    - Abolish classes in working agreement, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 67)
  - Sub-Series 477-135. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 135
    - Amend sick leave rule in Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac Railroad Agreement, 1943-1946 (Box 611b, Folder 68)
  - Sub-Series 477-136. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 136
    - Brotherhood demands jurisdiction over all freight handling in railroad warehouses, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 69)
  - Sub-Series 477-137. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 137
    - Change method of payment for handling United States mail, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 70)
  - Sub-Series 477-138. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 138
    - Discourage practice of requiring express managers to store freight at stations where no agent is on duty, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 71)
  - Sub-Series 477-139. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 139
    - Lend every effort to obtain passage of Federal Workmen's Compensation Act, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 72)
  - Sub-Series 477-140. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 140
    - Amend Railroad Retirement Act to provide pensions after 30 years' service, 60 years of age or after 20 years' service in physical disability cases, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 73)
  - Sub-Series 477-141. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 141
    - Amend Grand Lodge Constitution, Article 45, Section 8(b), to require General Chairmen to comply with Roberts' Rules of Order in System Board meetings, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 74)
  - Sub-Series 477-142. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 142
    - Amend Article 45, Section 15(a), to restrict per capita tax to System Boards to two-thirds of tax paid to Grand Lodge, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 75)
  - Sub-Series 477-143. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 143
    - Amend Grand Lodge Constitution, Article 45, Section 8(b) to require General Chairmen to open office to any member under jurisdiction of System Board, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 76)
  - Sub-Series 477-144. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 144
    - Amend Grand Lodge Constitution, Article 45, Section 5(a), to make formation of division protective committees compulsory, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 77)
  - Sub-Series 477-145. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 145
    - Establish legislative department in Grand Lodge and outline duties thereof, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 78)
  - Sub-Series 477-146. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 146
    - Vacation Agreement to provide vacations for employees in military service, the same as if in railroad service, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 79)
  - Sub-Series 477-147. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 147
    - Make Good Friday a legal holiday, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 80)
  - Sub-Series 477-148. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 148
    - That 35 years' service be sufficient for pension, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 81)
  - Sub-Series 477-149. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 149
    - Employees returning from military service be given vacation in year of return provided that they have 160 days' military service in that year, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 82)
  - Sub-Series 477-150. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 150
    - Request for draft deferment be approved by a joint labor-management committee before approval by a draft board, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 83)
  - Sub-Series 477-151. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 151
    - Brotherhood cooperate with other organizations to require management to furnish itemized statements of payroll deductions, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 84)
  - Sub-Series 477-152. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 152
    - If and when 40-hour week is secured, no employee shall be reduced below six days per week without increase in basic rate, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 85)
  - Sub-Series 477-153. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 153
    - Discipline to be administered only after hearing before an equal number of representatives of employee and management, with neutral referee, and that employee be permitted to continue working until investigation is held, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 86)
  - Sub-Series 477-154. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 154
    - Payments for illness or disability by Railroad Retirement Board after 30 days' absence from duty, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 87)
  - Sub-Series 477-155. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 155
    - Increase pensions of those already retired because of increased cost of living, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 88)
  - Sub-Series 477-156. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 156
    - Reinstate members who have been suspended while in military service without loss of benefits under the Death Benefit Department, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 89)
  - Sub-Series 477-157. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 157
    - General Chairmen to be required to make monthly report to each lodge under his jurisdiction., 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 90)
  - Sub-Series 477-158. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 158
    - Piece work and/or bonus system to be eliminated in Chicago switching district; rates of pay to be equalized and freight houses to be closed at 1:30 pm on Saturdays, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 91)
  - Sub-Series 477-159. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 159
    - Authorize Grand Executive Council to postpone 1947 Convention not to exceed one year after end of war, if national interest requires such postponement, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 92)
  - Sub-Series 477-160. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 160
    - Express appreciation to Pullman Company, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 93)
  - Sub-Series 477-161. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 161
    - Express appreciation to the railroads, hotels and other organizations in St. Louis, Missouri, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 94)
  - Sub-Series 477-162. 1943 Convention. Resolution No. 162
    - Express appreciation to the City of St. Louis local committee and District Council, 1943 (Box 611b, Folder 95)